{
    "id": "Cm0MGnuRnH0",
    "title": "Billie Eilish: Same Interview, One Year Apart | Vanity Fair",
    "numberOfQuestions": 10,
    "content": [
        {
            "question": "When was this video recorded?",
            "rightAnswer": 4,
            "answers": [
                "September 2017 and September 2018",
                "May 2016 and June 2018",
                "April 2016 and June 2011",
                "October 2017 and October 2018"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Billie Eilish in the video?",
            "rightAnswer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "15 and 16 years old",
                "14 and 15 years old",
                "15 and 17 years old",
                "15 and 11 years old"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "In 2017, Billie Eilish had __ Instagram followers.",
            "rightAnswer": 2,
            "answers": [
                "250,057",
                "257,000",
                "54,000",
                "1.4 M"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "Where was Billie Eilish’s best show?",
            "rightAnswer": 3,
            "answers": [
                "New York",
                "Vancouver",
                "Atlanta",
                "Los Angeles"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 129
        },
        {
            "question": "What advice did Billie Eilish give her future self?",
            "rightAnswer": 3,
            "answers": [
                "Don’t be content",
                "Be more popular",
                "Don’t be sad, it’s a waste of time",
                "It’s okay to be sad, it’s not a waste of time"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 230
        },
        {
            "question": "How does Billie Eilish handle pressure?",
            "rightAnswer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "Horribly",
                "Wonderfully",
                "Okay",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 522
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Billie Eilish enjoy most?",
            "rightAnswer": 2,
            "answers": [
                "Fame",
                "Shows and supporters",
                "Money",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 703
        },
        {
            "question": "Billie Eilish wants to visit ___ for the first time?",
            "rightAnswer": 2,
            "answers": [
                "China",
                "Japan",
                "Brazil",
                "Jamaica"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 821
        },
        {
            "question": "What are Billie Eilish’s two favorite colors?",
            "rightAnswer": 2,
            "answers": [
                "Light Blue and Black",
                "Light Green and Black",
                "Light Pink and Brown",
                "Dark Green and Black"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 841
        },
        {
            "question": "What new skill did Billie Eilish learn?",
            "rightAnswer": 4,
            "answers": [
                "How to sing better",
                "How to cook",
                "How to speak a new language",
                "How to drive"
            ],
            "timeInVideo": 1026
        }
    ]
}
